Register of the Henry Regnery Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Henry Regnery papers
1909-1996
82088
Hoover Institution Archives
139 manuscript boxes (58 linear feet)
Correspondence, memoranda, writings, legal and financial records, and printed matter, relating to publishing, and to conservative thought in the United States.
Regnery, Henry, 1912-
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1982.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
1912 Born, Hinsdale, Illinois
1934 Received B.S. in Mathematics from M.I.T.
1936 Attended Harvard University and received M.A. in Economics
1938-1941 Employed by the American Friends Service Committee
1947 Founded Regnery Publishing Company
1947-1966 President, Henry Regnery Company
1967-1977 Chairman of the Board, Henry Regnery Company
1977- President, Regnery and Gateway Company
Scope and Content Note
Correspondence, memoranda, writings, legal and financial records, and printed matter, relating to publishing, and to conservative thought in the United States.
Henry Regnery Company.; Conservatism.; Publishers and publishing---United States.; United States--Politics and government.
- Correspondence File, 1947-1978 (Box 1-81)
  Scope and Contents note
  Correspondence of Henry Regnery, arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent, except for a few files entered under subject. Includes some additional material such as drafts of writings, memoranda, and printed matter.
  - A (general) (Folder 1: 1)
  - Aaron, Larry, 1968 (Folder 1: 2)
  - Abbe, George, 1965-1967 (Folder 1: 3)
  - Abels, Jules, 1955-1960 (Folder 1: 4)
  - Abs, Herman J., 1957-1965 (Folder 1: 5)
  - Accame, Giano, 1961-1963 (Folder 1: 6)
  - Ackerman, Adolph J., 1961 (Folder 1: 7)
  - Acme News Company, 1966 (Folder 1: 8)
  - Adams, Wesley J., 1969 (Folder 1: 9)
  - Ade, George, 1963 (Folder 1: 10)
  - Adenauer, Konrad, 1964-1966 (Folder 1: 11)
  - Adler, Mortimer J., 1950-1962 (Folder 1: 12)
  - Ageton, Arthur A., 1952-1957 (Folder 1: 13)
  - Agnew, Spiro, 1977 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Akers, Milburn P., 1965 (Folder 2: 2)
  - Al-Aref, Aref, 1960 (Folder 2: 3)
  - Albrecht-Carrie, Else, 1978 (Folder 2: 4)
  - Albrecht, Karl I., 1956 (Folder 2: 5)
  - Aldington, Richard, 1955-1956 (Folder 2: 6)
  - Alexander, Anthony F., 1957-1968 (Folder 2: 7)
  - Alexander, Edgar, 1964-1966 (Folder 2: 8)
  - Alexander, Holmes, 1960-1976 (Folder 2: 9)
  - Alger, Bruce, 1963-1964 (Folder 2: 10)
  - Allen, Douglas Hedden, 1953-1954 (Folder 2: 11)
  - Allen (George) and Unwin Company, 1960-1966 (Folder 2: 12)
  - Allen, Knudsen, Swartz, Richardson and DeBoest (law firm), 1965 (Folder 2: 13)
  - Alsover, W. C., 1968-1969 (Folder 2: 14)
  - Alternative, 1970-1979 (Folder 2: 15)
  - Aly, Bower, 1968 (Folder 2: 16)
  - Amburn, Ellis, 1978 (Folder 2: 17)
  - America First Committee, 1951-1963 (Folder 2: 18)
  - American Academy of Public Affairs, 1957-1966 (Folder 2: 19)
  - American-African Affairs Association, 1965-1967 (Folder 2: 20)
  - American Book Company, 1966 (Folder 2: 21)
  - American Book Publishers Council, 1956-1966 (Folder 2: 22)
  - American Conservative Union, 1964-1969 (Folder 2: 23)
  - American Council on Germany. (Folder 2: 24)
    Includes report by Christopher Emmet, 1961-1965
  - American Economic Foundation, 1960-1966 (Folder 2: 25)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1962-1966 (Folder 3: 1)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1965-1966 (Folder 3: 2)
  - American Foundation of Religion and Psychiatry, 1964-1965 (Folder 3: 3)
  - American Friends of the Middle East, 1954-1966 (Folder 3: 4)
  - American Friends Service Committtee, 1946-1948 (Folder 3: 5)
  - American Library Association, 1957-1964 (Folder 3: 6)
  - American Political Science Association, 1964 (Folder 3: 7)
  - American Publishers Corporation, 1966-1967 (Folder 3: 8)
  - American Purpose, 1963 (Folder 3: 9)
  - American Security Council, 1957-1967 (Folder 3: 10)
  - Americanism Educational League, 1964-1966 (Folder 3: 11)
  - Americans for Conservative Action, 1965 (Folder 3: 12)
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1961 (Folder 3: 13)
  - America's Future, Inc., 1963-1971 (Folder 3: 14)
  - Anastaplo, George, 1967-1968 (Folder 3: 15)
  - Anders, W., 1953 (Folder 3: 16)
  - Anderson, James F., 1968-1978 (Folder 3: 17)
  - Anderson, Per-Olow, 1960-1968 (Folder 3: 18)
  - Andic, Martin, 1977 (Folder 3: 19)
  - Andreiw, Matt, 1978 (Folder 3: 20)
  - Andres, Stefan, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Andreyev, Vladimir. (Folder 4: 2)
    Includes correspondence with Fred P. Berry, 1961-1962
  - Anisimov, Oleg, 1951-1957 (Folder 4: 3)
  - Anti-Communist League of America, 1956-1957 (Folder 4: 4)
  - Anti-Communist Liaison (organization), 1963-1964 (Folder 4: 5)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1954-1964 (Folder 4: 6)
  - Antoniades, John (Mrs.), 1969 (Folder 4: 7)
  - Appleby, Stanley, 1968-1969 (Folder 4: 8)
  - Arab Information Center, 1965-1966 (Folder 4: 9)
  - Arbatsky, Yury, 1951-1952 (Folder 4: 10)
  - Arbeitsgemeinschaft, 1965-1966 (Folder 4: 11)
  - Areilza, Jose Maria de, 1955 (Folder 4: 12)
  - Arendt, Hannah, 1962 (Folder 4: 13)
  - Arnold, Eberhard C. H., 1949-1960 (Folder 4: 14)
  - Aron, Raymond, 1977-1978 (Folder 4: 15)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1968 (Folder 4: 16)
  - Artemis Verlag, 1967 (Folder 4: 17)
  - Artemiev, Vyacheslav P., 1962-1966 (Folder 4: 18)
  - Ashbrook, John M., 1969 (Folder 4: 19)
  - Ashe, Alicia, 1968 (Folder 4: 20)
  - Ashkin, David, 1968 (Folder 4: 21)
  - Ashton, E. B., 1961-1963 (Folder 4: 22)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1961-1965 (Folder 4: 23)
  - Athenaeum Verlag, 1966 (Folder 4: 24)
  - Atkinson, James D., 1956-1968 (Folder 4: 25)
  - Atlantik-Bruecke, 1966 (Folder 4: 26)
  - Attwater, Donald, 1950 (Folder 4: 27)
  - Aubier editions Montaigne, 1963 (Folder 4: 28)
  - Auden, W. H., 1964-1968 (Folder 4: 29)
  - Aungst, Ronald L., 1969 (Folder 4: 30)
  - Authors Guild, 1964 (Folder 4: 31)
  - Avtorkhanov, Abdurakhman, 1965-1966 (Folder 4: 32)
  - Ayer, Frederick Jr., 1957-1973 (Folder 4: 33)
  - B (general) (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Baarslag, Karl H. W., 1951-1979 (Folder 5: 2)
  - Babbitt, Irving, 1956 (Folder 5: 3)
  - Babcock, Frederic, 1963 (Folder 5: 4)
  - Bach, Julian S., Jr., 1963-1966 (Folder 5: 5)
  - Bailey, Douglas L., 1963 (Folder 5: 6)
  - Bailey, George, 1969-1979 (Folder 5: 7)
  - Bailey, Herbert, 1972 (Folder 5: 8)
  - Bailey and Swinfen Company, 1967 (Folder 5: 9)
  - Baker, Selma (Mrs.), 1968 (Folder 5: 10)
  - Baldwin, Rosecrans, 1970-1976 (Folder 5: 11)
  - Ball, George, 1970-1978 (Folder 5: 12)
  - Ball, Stuart S., 1969-1977 (Folder 5: 13)
  - Barnard, Harry, 1968 (Folder 5: 14)
  - Barnes, Harry Elmer, 1947-1957 (Folder 5: 15)
  - Barnes, Harry Elmer, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Barnett, Frank R., 1953-1972 (Folder 6: 2)
  - Barr, Charles R., 1962-1965 (Folder 6: 3)
  - Barr, Dwight L., 1969 (Folder 6: 4)
  - Barraclough, Geoffrey, 1947 (Folder 6: 5)
  - Barrody, Bill, 1969 (Folder 6: 6)
  - Barth, Karl, 1949 (Folder 6: 7)
  - Bartley, Robert L., 1978 (Folder 6: 8)
  - Barwig, Regis N., 1967-1968 (Folder 6: 9)
  - Barzun, Jacques, 1949 (Folder 6: 10)
  - Bassiouni, M. Cherif, 1978 (Folder 6: 11)
  - Batterman, Steven C., 1969 (Folder 6: 12)
  - Bauder, Frank, 1970-1972 (Folder 6: 13)
  - Baum, L. Frank, 1967 (Folder 6: 14)
  - Beadle, Muriel, 1971-1973 (Folder 6: 15)
  - Beatty, Ilene, 1968 (Folder 6: 16)
  - Beaumont, William H., 1968 (Folder 6: 17)
  - Bechtle (Richard) Graphische Betriebe und Verlags-gesellschaft, 1960-1967 (Folder 6: 18)
  - Becker, Kenneth, 1946-1967 (Folder 6: 19)
  - Becker, Maximilian, 1967 (Folder 6: 20)
  - Beckett, James D., 1971-1972 (Folder 6: 21)
  - Beeby, Betty, 1960 (Folder 6: 22)
  - Beleckas, Joseph P., 1953-1965 (Folder 6: 23)
  - Belgion, Montgomery. Includes correspondence with widow Helen Belgion, 1948-1962 (Folder 6: 24)
  - Bell, Bernard Iddings, 1948-1955 (Folder 7: 1)
  - Benda, Clemens E., 1968-1971 (Folder 7: 2)
  - Bennett, Charles Dana, 1946-1974 (Folder 7: 3)
  - Benson, George S., 1955-1964 (Folder 7: 4)
  - Berger, Elmer E., 1977 (Folder 7: 5)
  - Berger, Hans, 1952 (Folder 7: 6)
  - Bergstraesser, Arnold, 1948-1952 (Folder 7: 7)
  - Bergstroesse, Erike, 1965 (Folder 7: 8)
  - Berns, Walter F., 1964-1967 (Folder 7: 9)
  - Bertram Rota Company, 1967-1970 (Folder 7: 10)
  - Beston, Henry, 1947 (Folder 7: 11)
  - Bethell, Ruth Mary, 1955 (Folder 7: 12)
  - Bettin, John, 1968 (Folder 7: 13)
  - Beum, Robert, 1964-1977 (Folder 7: 14)
  - Biederstein Verlag Muenchen, 1962-1966 (Folder 7: 15)
  - Biermann, Georg, 1947 (Folder 7: 16)
  - Bird, Christopher, 1956-1963 (Folder 7: 17)
  - Bittner (H.) and Company, 1945-1950 (Folder 7: 18)
  - Bittner, Herbert, 1949 (Folder 7: 19)
  - Bittner, Herbert, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Black, Max, 1968 (Folder 8: 2)
  - Blake, Robert W., 1960-1970 (Folder 8: 3)
  - Block, David M., 1969 (Folder 8: 4)
  - Blodgett, John W., Jr., 1947-1978 (Folder 8: 5)
  - Boarman, Patrick M., 1955-1969 (Folder 8: 6)
  - Bobbitt, Mary Reed, 1960-1967 (Folder 8: 7)
  - Bobbitt, Vernon, 1978 (Folder 8: 8)
  - Bock, Eugene, 1968 (Folder 8: 9)
  - Bodley Head Company, 1961-1968 (Folder 8: 10)
  - Boeker, Alexander, 1947-1978 (Folder 8: 11)
  - Bogan, Louise, 1949-1968 (Folder 8: 12)
  - Bogolepov, Igor, 1953-1954 (Folder 8: 13)
  - Bolin, Luis A., 1963-1964 (Folder 8: 14)
  - Bolling, Landrum R., 1970 (Folder 8: 15)
  - Bollingen Foundation, 1966-1967 (Folder 8: 16)
  - Book of the Month Club, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - Bookmailer Company, 1966-1968 (Folder 9: 2)
  - Booksales Company, 1966 (Folder 9: 3)
  - Boorstin, Daniel, 1967-1974 (Folder 9: 4)
  - Borchard, Edwin M., 1946-1948 (Folder 9: 5)
  - Borchardt, Georges, 1956-1967 (Folder 9: 6)
  - Borghese, J. Valerio, 1954 (Folder 9: 7)
  - Borland, Bruce D., 1977-1978 (Folder 9: 8)
  - Borniman, Alfred H., 1967-1978 (Folder 9: 9)
  - Boulware, Lemuel R., 1965-1971 (Folder 9: 10)
  - Bouscaren, Anthony Trawick, 1954-1977 (Folder 9: 11)
  - Boveri, Margret A., 1963-1966 (Folder 9: 12)
  - Bozell, L. Brent, 1952-1972 (Folder 9: 13)
  - Bradford, M. E., 1970-1977 (Folder 9: 14)
  - Bradley, Mark A., 1977-1978 (Folder 9: 15)
  - Brady, William H., Jr., 1956-1968 (Folder 9: 16)
  - Brandt, Karl, 1946-1966 (Folder 9: 17)
  - Branick, Vincent, 1978 (Folder 9: 18)
  - Braun, Freiherr von, 1951-1967 (Folder 9: 19)
  - Braunfeld, Allan, 1969-1978 (Folder 9: 20)
  - Bredvold, Louis I., 1968 (Folder 9: 21)
  - Breeskin, Mrs., 1967 (Folder 9: 22)
  - Briefs, Elinor, 1955 (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - Briefs, Goetz, 1954-1971 (Folder 10: 2)
  - Bro, Kenneth A., 1968-1969 (Folder 10: 3)
  - Bro, Margueritte H., 1962-1971 (Folder 10: 4)
  - Brooks, Amanda Wallace, 1977 (Folder 10: 5)
  - Brown, Constantine, 1953-1969 (Folder 10: 6)
  - Brown, Edmond R., 1969 (Folder 10: 7)
  - Brown, Frank London, 1960 (Folder 10: 8)
  - Brown (William C.) Company, 1957-1966 (Folder 10: 9)
  - Browning, Norma Lee, 1962-1968 (Folder 10: 10)
  - Buchanan, Patrick J., 1977 (Folder 10: 11)
  - Buchinger, Hans W., 1966-1967 (Folder 10: 12)
  - Buckley, James C., 1971-1973 (Folder 10: 13)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1951-1968 (Folder 10: 14)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1968 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Buckley, William F., Sr., 1954-1966 (Folder 11: 2)
  - Budberg, Baroness Moura, 1947 (Folder 11: 3)
  - Budenz, Louis Francis, 1951-1971 (Folder 11: 4)
  - Burch, Dean, 1967-1968 (Folder 11: 5)
  - Burke, Arleigh A., 1961 (Folder 11: 6)
  - Burlinson, John J., Jr., 1964-1977 (Folder 11: 7)
  - Burnett, Leo, 1965 (Folder 11: 8)
  - Burnham, James, 1955-1974 (Folder 11: 9)
  - Burns, James MacGregor, 1967 (Folder 11: 10)
  - Burns and Oates Company, 1957-1966 (Folder 11: 11)
  - Business-Industry Political Action Committee, 1964-1966 (Folder 11: 12)
  - Butler, Richard, 1956-1961 (Folder 11: 13)
  - Buzby, Carroll, 1968 (Folder 11: 14)
  - Byrne, John F., 1962 (Folder 11: 15)
  - C (general) (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - Cain, Seymour, 1956 (Folder 12: 2)
  - Cairns, Huntington, 1960-1976 (Folder 12: 3)
  - Caldwell, John C., 1952-1957 (Folder 12: 4)
  - California Teachers Association, 1961 (Folder 12: 5)
  - Cameron, J. M., 1947-1973 (Folder 12: 6)
  - Campaigne, Jameson G., 1960-1977 (Folder 12: 7)
  - Campbell, Albert M., 1968-1977 (Folder 12: 8)
  - Campbell, Glenn, 1971-1974 (Folder 12: 9)
  - Campbell, Mary, 1967-1978 (Folder 12: 10)
  - Caponigri, A. Robert, 1952-1978 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Cappelletti, Mauro, 1970 (Folder 13: 2)
  - Captive Nations Week, 1960 (Folder 13: 3)
  - Caralt, Luis de, 1966 (Folder 13: 4)
  - Carfagno, Vincent R., 1968-1978 (Folder 13: 5)
  - Carleton, Milton, 1968-1978 (Folder 13: 6)
  - Carroll, Louis D., 1955-1956 (Folder 13: 7)
  - Carroll, Owen, 1963 (Folder 13: 8)
  - Carroll, Paul, 1957 (Folder 13: 9)
  - Carter, Hodding, 1961 (Folder 13: 10)
  - Carter, Thomas H., 1961 (Folder 13: 11)
  - Carus, M. Blouke, 1971-1972 (Folder 13: 12)
  - Casey, William J., 1952-1978 (Folder 13: 13)
  - Caspari, Fritz, 1946-1976 (Folder 13: 14)
  - Casserley, J. V. Langmead, 1966 (Folder 13: 15)
  - Cassidy, Victor, 1970-1977 (Folder 13: 16)
  - Castle, Eugene W., 1955-1957 (Folder 13: 17)
  - Catlin, George, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Cavalcade of Books Company, 1965 (Folder 14: 2)
  - Caxton Printers, 1955-1965 (Folder 14: 3)
  - Center for Strategic Studies, 1966 (Folder 14: 4)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1960-1975 (Folder 14: 5)
  - Central National Bank (Chicago), 1971 (Folder 14: 6)
  - Cervantes, Lucius F., 1955-1962 (Folder 14: 7)
  - Chalmers, Burns, 1969-1978 (Folder 14: 8)
  - Chalmers, Gordon K., 1951-1957 (Folder 14: 9)
  - Chamberlain, John, 1951-1979 (Folder 14: 10)
  - Chamberlin, William Henry, 1950-1969 (Folder 14: 11)
  - Chambers, Whittaker, 1967 (Folder 14: 12)
  - Cheshire (F. W.) Pty. Company, 1965-1979 (Folder 14: 13)
  - Chicago Daily News, 1968-1969 (Folder 14: 14)
  - Chicago Sun-Times, 1968 (Folder 14: 15)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1967 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Chicago Tribune, 1967-1974 (Folder 15: 2)
  - Chicago's American, 1967-1968 (Folder 15: 3)
  - Chih-mai, Chen, 1955 (Folder 15: 4)
  - Childrens Press, 1966 (Folder 15: 5)
  - Chilton Company, 1960-1967 (Folder 15: 6)
  - Chodorov, Frank, 1946-1955 (Folder 15: 7)
  - Choice, 1966 (Folder 15: 8)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1949-1967 (Folder 15: 9)
  - Christianform (organization), 1953 (Folder 15: 10)
  - Clay, Lucius D., 1959-1970 (Folder 15: 11)
  - Coase, Ronald H., 1968-1977 (Folder 15: 12)
  - Collier, David S., 1967-1979 (Folder 15: 13)
  - Collier, Oscar, 1969 (Folder 15: 14)
  - Collins, James, 1951-1978 (Folder 15: 15)
  - Collins, William M., 1968 (Folder 15: 16)
  - Collins (William) Sons and Company, 1963-1964 (Folder 15: 17)
  - Combined Insurance Company of America, 1969 (Folder 15: 18)
  - Committee for a Conservative Catholic Magazine, 1965 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Committee on Discussion and Debate (National University Extension Association), 1963-1965 (Folder 16: 2)
  - Conservative Book Club, 1965-1978 (Folder 16: 3)
  - Conservative Books by Mail Company, 1967 (Folder 16: 4)
  - Conservatives' Meeting, 1953 (Folder 16: 5)
  - Constructive Action, Inc., 1964-1971 (Folder 16: 6)
  - Cope, Thomas P., 1976-1979 (Folder 16: 7)
  - Copp Clark Publishing Company, 1966 (Folder 16: 8)
  - Cook, Deborah N., 1977 (Folder 16: 9)
  - Core, George, 1967-1968 (Folder 16: 10)
  - Cornuelle, Herbert C., 1964-1965 (Folder 16: 11)
  - Cornuelle, Richard C., 1960-1966 (Folder 16: 12)
  - Cosmo Book Distributing Company, 1967 (Folder 16: 13)
  - Cotton, W. Philip, Jr., 1967-1968 (Folder 16: 14)
  - Costa, Ildefonsa, 1969 (Folder 16: 15)
  - Costikyan, Edward N., 1969 (Folder 16: 16)
  - Couch, William T., 1951-1976 (Folder 16: 17)
  - Coulter, Thomas H., 1950-1975 (Folder 16: 18)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1963-1966 (Folder 16: 19)
  - Council for Basic Education, 1960-1978 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs, 1967 (Folder 17: 2)
  - Cousins, Norman, 1977 (Folder 17: 3)
  - Cowling, Donald J., 1965 (Folder 17: 4)
  - Cox, Howard Ellis, 1968 (Folder 17: 5)
  - Cox, Morris A., 1970-1975 (Folder 17: 6)
  - Cox, Steve, 1977-1978 (Folder 17: 7)
  - Crane, Philip M., 1964-1972 (Folder 17: 8)
  - Crippen, John K., 1969 (Folder 17: 9)
  - Crocker, George N., 1960-1976 (Folder 17: 10)
  - Crunden, Robert M., 1966 (Folder 17: 11)
  - Csikszentmihalyi, Mihaly, 1968 (Folder 17: 12)
  - Cummings, Tilden (Mrs.), 1968 (Folder 17: 13)
  - Cummings, Walter J., Jr., 1953-1966 (Folder 17: 14)
  - Cummins, Nicholas C., 1968-1976 (Folder 17: 15)
  - Curtis Brown Company, 1957-1965 (Folder 17: 16)
  - Curtis Circulation Company, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Curtis, Ever, 1968 (Folder 18: 2)
  - Czarnecki, Katerina, 1978 (Folder 18: 3)
  - Czugunow, T., 1966 (Folder 18: 4)
  - D (general) (Folder 18: 5)
  - Dallin, David J., 1948-1965 (Folder 18: 6)
  - Danby, Hope, 1950 (Folder 18: 7)
  - Danielsson, Bengt, 1966 (Folder 18: 8)
  - Darton, Longman and Todd Company, 1955-1967 (Folder 18: 9)
  - Davenport, John, 1957-1972 (Folder 18: 10)
  - Daves, Melissa M., 1968 (Folder 18: 11)
  - Davidson, Donald, 1964 (Folder 18: 12)
  - Davidson, Eugene, 1948-1956 (Folder 18: 13)
  - Davidson, Eugene, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Davis, Albert D., 1965-1966 (Folder 19: 2)
  - Davis, John H., 1968 (Folder 19: 3)
  - Davis, W. Jefferson, 1968 (Folder 19: 4)
  - DeCleva, Paul, 1972-1978 (Folder 19: 5)
  - Dehmlow, Louis H.T., 1954-1977 (Folder 19: 6)
  - Delaney, Robert F., 1957 (Folder 19: 7)
  - DeLuca, Peter, 1969-1977 (Folder 19: 8)
  - Derwinski, Edward J., 1966 (Folder 19: 9)
  - De Toledano, Ralph, 1952-1977 (Folder 19: 10)
  - Deutsche Verlags-Anstalt Stuttgart, 1960-1971 (Folder 19: 11)
  - Devin-Adair Company, 1956-1967 (Folder 19: 12)
  - Devine, Donald J., 1977 (Folder 19: 13)
  - De Witte, Ruth Tensen, 1968-1978 (Folder 19: 14)
  - Diamond, Sigmund, 1968 (Folder 19: 15)
  - Dickson, Richard H., Jr., 1964-1966 (Folder 19: 16)
  - Diehl, Guenter, 1962-1965 (Folder 19: 17)
  - Dietrich, Otto, 1955-1971 (Folder 19: 18)
  - Dietze, Gottfried, 1955-1969 (Folder 19: 19)
  - Dimension Books, 1965-198 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Dittoro, M., 1978 (Folder 20: 2)
  - Diwakar, R. R., 1949-1953 (Folder 20: 3)
  - Doenecke, Justus D., 1970-1977 (Folder 20: 4)
  - Doering, Otto C., 1949-1953 (Folder 20: 5)
  - Domes, Alfred, 1961-1978 (Folder 20: 6)
  - Donald, Alice A., 1978 (Folder 20: 7)
  - Donner, Robert, 1960-1970 (Folder 20: 8)
  - Dorn, Frank, 1953 (Folder 20: 9)
  - Dos Passos, John, 1956-1970 (Folder 20: 10)
  - Doubleday and Company, 1967 (Folder 20: 11)
  - Down, A. Graham, 1977 (Folder 20: 12)
  - Downer, Alan S., 1967 (Folder 20: 13)
  - Drake, Robert, 1974-1977 (Folder 20: 14)
  - Draskovich, Slobodan M., 1957-1966 (Folder 20: 15)
  - Dresdner Bank, 1969 (Folder 20: 16)
  - Driscoll, Thomas G., 1968 (Folder 20: 17)
  - Dunham, Allison, 1960-1970 (Folder 20: 18)
  - Durand Dorr Supply Company, 1968 (Folder 20: 19)
  - E (general) (Folder 20: 20)
  - Earhart Foundation, 1956-1977 (Folder 20: 21)
  - Eastman, Max, 1951-1957 (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - Eberstadt, Ferdinand, 1965-1966 (Folder 21: 2)
  - Ebony Magazine, 1968-1969 (Folder 21: 3)
  - Eggleston, George T., 1974-1977 (Folder 21: 4)
  - Ehrenburg, Ilya, n.d. (Folder 21: 5)
  - Eitel, Otto K., 1949-1972 (Folder 21: 6)
  - Eliasberg, George J., 1950 (Folder 21: 7)
  - Ely (Fred D.) Company, 1965-1967 (Folder 21: 8)
  - Emlen, Alan L., 1977 (Folder 21: 9)
  - Emmet, Christopher, 1966-1970 (Folder 21: 10)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1962-1964 (Folder 21: 11)
  - Engle, Paul, 1952 (Folder 21: 12)
  - Episcopal Book Club, 1967 (Folder 21: 13)
  - Espaillat, Arturo R., 1963-1964 (Folder 21: 14)
  - Evans, E. Stanton, 1960-1979 (Folder 21: 15)
  - Evans, Ernestine, 1949 (Folder 21: 16)
  - Evans, Glade A., 1968 (Folder 21: 17)
  - Evans, James R., 1978 (Folder 21: 18)
  - Evans, Medford, 1956 (Folder 21: 19)
  - Evans, William, 1967-1971 (Folder 21: 20)
  - Evarts, Effingham, 1954 (Folder 21: 21)
  - Ewing, George W., 1964 (Folder 21: 22)
  - F (general) (Folder 21: 23)
  - Faber, Nancy W., 1962-1972 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Faber and Faber Company, 1961-1965 (Folder 22: 2)
  - Fanget, Louis, 1967 (Folder 22: 3)
  - Farm Bureau Federation, 1965 (Folder 22: 4)
  - Farnsworth, Clyde A., 1972-1974 (Folder 22: 5)
  - Farnsworth, Edith, 1968-1971 (Folder 22: 6)
  - Fawcett World Library, 1963-1966 (Folder 22: 7)
  - Feldenkirchen, Toni, 1969 (Folder 22: 8)
  - Fellers, Bonner, 1949-1967 (Folder 22: 9)
  - Fertig, Lawrence, 1961-1968 (Folder 22: 10)
  - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr., 1971-1977 (Folder 22: 11)
  - Field, Marshall, 1969 (Folder 22: 12)
  - Finley, Harold M., 1964-1967 (Folder 22: 13)
  - First National Bank of Chicago, 1977 (Folder 22: 14)
  - Fischer, Hanns, 1965-1971 (Folder 22: 15)
  - Fischer (S.) Verlag, 1966 (Folder 22: 16)
  - Fish, George W., 1977 (Folder 22: 17)
  - Fisher, Anthony, 1970-1975 (Folder 22: 18)
  - Fitch, Geraldine, 1956-1971 (Folder 22: 19)
  - Fitzpatrick, William J., 1966-1967 (Folder 22: 20)
  - Flaherty, Daniel L., 1968 (Folder 22: 21)
  - Fleischauer, Warren L., 1955 (Folder 22: 22)
  - Flynn, Maureen, 1957 (Folder 22: 23)
  - Foley, Louis, 1977 (Folder 22: 24)
  - Fontaine, Dorothy de, 1965 (Folder 22: 25)
  - Foschini, Bernard M., 1957-1978 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 1956-1977 (Folder 23: 2)
  - Foundation for Foreign Affairs, 1947-1967 (Folder 23: 3)
  - Fowlie, Wallace, 1957-1978 (Folder 23: 4)
  - Fox, Charles Philip, 1963-1972 (Folder 23: 5)
  - Franco, Francisco, 1954 (Folder 23: 6)
  - Francois-Ponet, Andre, 1966 (Folder 23: 7)
  - Franke, David, 1968-1977 (Folder 23: 8)
  - Franzone, David E., 1968 (Folder 23: 9)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia, 1963 (Folder 23: 10)
  - Freemantle, Anne, 1948 (Folder 23: 11)
  - French Consulate General, Chicago, 1963-1964 (Folder 23: 12)
  - French Embassy, Washington D. C., 1965 (Folder 23: 13)
  - Freund, Ludwig, 1956-1967 (Folder 23: 14)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1966-1971 (Folder 23: 15)
  - Fringes, Manfred S., 1977 (Folder 23: 16)
  - Fritz Knapp Verlag, 1961-1966 (Folder 23: 17)
  - Frost, Lesley, 1952 (Folder 23: 18)
  - G (general) (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Gallery, Daniel V., 1946-1967 (Folder 24: 2)
  - Gallery, John Ireland, 1956-1965 (Folder 24: 3)
  - Gallimard Editions, 1966 (Folder 24: 4)
  - Galvin, Robert W., 1966-1979 (Folder 24: 5)
  - Gardner, W. H., 1960-1964 (Folder 24: 6)
  - Garrett, Garet, 1947-1955 (Folder 24: 7)
  - Garrison, Winfred, 1965-1967 (Folder 24: 8)
  - Garrity, Devin A., 1970-1979 (Folder 24: 9)
  - Gaskins, Thomas, 1961-1973 (Folder 24: 10)
  - Gateway Editions, 1977-1979 (Folder 24: 11)
  - Gauquelin, Michel, 1966 (Folder 24: 12)
  - Gazzaniga, Michael S., 1965-1966 (Folder 24: 13)
  - Gebrueder Mann, Verlag, 1956-1965 (Folder 24: 14)
  - German Embassy, Washington D.C., 1960-1966 (Folder 24: 15)
  - German Information Center, 1962-1971 (Folder 24: 16)
  - Gheorghiu, Virgil, 1966-1969 (Folder 24: 17)
  - Gibney, Frank B., 1956-1961 (Folder 24: 18)